Are you ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
KIDS:
Aye, aye, Captain.
儿童：
是的，是的，船长。
I can't hear you.
我听不到你说话。
Aye, aye, Captain!
是啊是啊，队长！
♪ Oh...
♪ 哦...
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants!♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！♪
♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants!♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！♪
♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
♪ 如果是航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants!♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！♪
♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants!♪Ready?
♪ 海绵宝宝！♪ 准备好了吗？
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants!
♪ 海绵宝宝！
[ hearty laughter]
[爽朗的笑声]
Captioning sponsored by
MTV NETWORKS
字幕赞助商
MTV 网络
One Monster
Krabby Patty, please.
一只怪物
克拉比帕蒂，请。
Humph. No one's ordered
a Monster Patty in ages.
哼。没有人下单
多年来的怪物帕蒂。
SpongeBob?
海绵宝宝？
One Monster Krabby Patty.
一只怪物蟹蟹帕蒂。
D-d-did you say
a M-Monster Krabby Patty?
D-D-你说
M-Monster 蟹黄派蒂？
Uh, one Monster Krabby Patty.
呃，一只怪物蟹蟹帕蒂。
Huh?
啊？
Monster Krabby Patty?
怪物蟹蟹帕蒂？
ALL:
Monster Krabby Patty?
全部：
怪物蟹蟹帕蒂？
[ toilet flushing]Monster Krabby Patty?
[冲厕所]怪物蟹蟹帕蒂？
Oh, dear Neptune.
哦，亲爱的海王星。
Oh, boy.
哦，男孩。
We can do this!
我们可以做到这一点！
At the count of three, we flip!
数到三，我们翻转！
Ready?
准备好？
One...
一...
two...
二...
three!
三！
[ spatula snaps]Oh... bad.
[抹刀啪地一声]哦……糟糕。
[ screaming]
[尖叫]
[ squeaking]
[吱吱声]
[ screaming]
[尖叫]
[ wailing]
[哀嚎]
[ wailing][ wailing]
[哀嚎][哀嚎]
[ wailing]
[哀嚎]
Mm-hmm.
嗯嗯。
Go on.
继续。
[ wailing]
[哀嚎]
[ siren wailing]
[警笛哀嚎]
[ door shuts]
[门关上]
[ tires screeching]
[轮胎吱吱作响]
Well, we'd better
get back to work.
嗯，我们最好
回去工作吧。
Work?
工作？
How could I go back to work
without...
我怎样才能回去工作
没有...
without Spat?!
没有口角？！
Use another spatula.
使用另一把抹刀。
What?!
什么？！
There is only one spatula
for me,
只有一把锅铲
对我来说，
and that is Spat.
那就是吐口水。
Spat, wait up! Spat!
吐槽，等等！吐口水！
I'm coming, Spat!
我来了，斯帕特！
[ beeping]
[嘟嘟声]
Oh, Spat.
哦，斯帕特。
We've been through
so much together.
我们已经经历过
在一起这么多。
[ sizzling]
[铁板]
[ laughing]
[笑]
Oh...
哦...
uh-huh...
呃呃...
[ clanking]
[叮当作响]
[ laughing]
[笑]
[ screaming]
[尖叫]
[ laughing]
[笑]
There's no easy way
to say this.
没有简单的方法
说这个。
SpongeBob, if I were you,
海绵宝宝，如果我是你，
I would give serious
consideration
我会认真的
考虑
to start thinking about...
a replacement spatula.
开始思考...
替换抹刀。
[ whimpering]
[呜咽]
Go home, get some rest.
回家休息吧。
We'll... try to do
everything we can.
我们会...尝试做
我们能做的一切。
Thank you, Doctor.
谢谢你，医生。
Oh, I'm not a doctor.
哦，我不是医生。
I'm an actor
researching for a role.
我是一名演员
研究角色。
Yes! Whoo-hoo!
是的！呼呼！
I am so totally
gonna get this part!
我是如此彻底
会得到这个部分！
[ sighs]
[叹气]
[ sniffling]
[抽鼻子]
Replacement spatula?
更换抹刀？
How could anything
ever replace...
怎么可能有事
曾经更换...
Hey, look at that!
嘿，看看那个！
Ooh!
哦！
Looks fancy.
看起来很别致。
So shiny...
如此闪亮...
Oh, those lines, so... sleek.
哦，那些线条，如此……光滑。
What am I talking about?
我在说什么？
I don't need this!
我不需要这个！
Maybe I do need this.
也许我确实需要这个。
I would give serious
consideration to...
我会认真的
考虑到...
[ gong chimes]
[锣声]
...a replacement spatula.
...替换抹刀。
Ow!
噢！
Uh-uh. No touchy-touchy
the Le Spatula.
呃呃。不敏感不敏感
锅铲。
It's very, very
expensive.
I'm sorry.
这是非常非常
昂贵。
对不起。
Of course, if you
purchase this fine item,
当然，如果你
购买这件精美的商品，
you may... hold it.
你可以……坚持住。
Well, I've got some
loose change in my pocket.
嗯，我有一些
我口袋里的零钱。
Will this cover it?
这个会覆盖吗？
Um....
嗯……
mm, mm, mm...
mm, mm, mm, mm, mm...
毫米，毫米，毫米……
毫米，毫米，毫米，毫米，毫米……
mm...
毫米...
No.
不。
How about now?
现在怎么样？
No.
不。
Now?
现在？
No.
不。
Now?
No.
现在？
不。
Now?
No.
现在？
不。
Now?
No.
现在？
不。
[ high-pitched blurt]
[高亢的脱口而出]
Now?
现在？
No.
不。
That's everything I have.
这就是我所拥有的一切。
Now can I buy Le Spatula?
现在我可以购买 Le Spatula 吗？
Everything, huh?
一切，是吗？
Nice outfit.
不错的衣服。
[ singing happily]
[快乐地唱歌]
Good evening, sir.
晚上好，先生。
Yaah!
呀啊！
[ whistling]
[吹口哨]
Hmph!
哼！
Oh!
Hey, Granny,
what's shakin'?
哦！
嘿，奶奶，
什么在摇晃？
[ singing]
[唱歌]
[ continues singing]
[继续唱歌]
Mm, breezy today, heh.
嗯，今天风很大，呵呵。
Nice outfit, SpongeBob!
海绵宝宝，这套衣服不错！
[ snorting, guffawing]
[哼哼，大笑]
Thanks, Squidward.
谢谢，章鱼哥。
It was worth
every penny.
这是值得的
每一分钱。
What's all
the lollygagging about?!
全部是什么
棒棒糖呕吐有关？！
Mr. Krabs,
get a load of SpongeBob!
蟹老板先生，
得到海绵宝宝的负载！
[ cackling]This better be good!
[咯咯笑]这最好是好的！
[ singing happily]
[快乐地唱歌]
Soon everyone will know
of your beauty.
很快大家就会知道
你的美丽。
All right,
what's going on in... Oh!
好吧，
这是怎么回事……哦！
Don't you have
any shame, boy?
你没有吗
有什么羞耻的吗，孩子？
All my shame went in here,
Mr. Krabs.
我所有的耻辱都集中在这里，
蟹老板。
KRABS:
Le Spa-tu-ler!
螃蟹：
Le Spa-tu-ler！
What in blazes isthat?
火焰中那是什么？
Oh, just the answer to our
little production dilemma.
哦，这只是我们的答案
生产困境不大。
Well, what can it do?
嗯，它能做什么呢？
Can it make me famous?
能让我出名吗？
Anything you want and more!
任何你想要的，甚至更多！
Ooh, that sounds exciting.
哦，听起来很令人兴奋。
Let me have a go at it!
让我来试试吧！
Oh, I'm sorry, Mr. Krabs,
no can do.
哦，对不起，蟹老板，
没有可以做的。
What?! Are you going against
your commanding officer?
什么？！你反对吗
你的指挥官？
No, it's not that.
不，不是那样的。
It's just that this is a highly
developed piece of engineering
只是这是一个高度
开发的工程
that takes quality time
to master.
这需要优质的时间
掌握。
With that fancy machinery,
I expect you
有了那些奇特的机械，
to make Krabby Patties
twice as fast.
制作蟹黄饼
速度快两倍。
Oh, I don't think
that'll be a problem, Mr. Krabs.
哦，我不认为
这将是一个问题，蟹老板。
In fact...
实际上...
[ French accent]:
Le Spatula 3000,
[法国口音]：
抹刀 3000，
at your service.
竭诚为您服务。
Huh! Impressive.
哈！感人的。
Well, let's see that thing
impress me even more--
好吧，让我们看看那个东西
更让我印象深刻的是——
by bringing in
more customers
通过引入
更多客户
and more money
in me pocket.
和更多的钱
[ chuckling]
[轻笑]
Oh, you won't believe what
Le Spatula is capable of.
哦，你不会相信什么
Le Spatula 有能力。
Ready to show 'em, buddy?
准备好向他们展示了吗，伙计？
Oh, it's okay,
no need to be shy.
哦，没关系，
无需害羞。
It's always tough
the first day on the job.
总是很难
Uh, can I get one
Krabby Patty, please?
呃，我可以买一个吗
克拉比帕蒂，可以吗？
SpongeBob, I need
one Krabby Patty.
海绵宝宝，我需要
一份蟹肉饼。
One Krabby Patty coming up
lickety-split.
一只蟹肉饼即将登场
迅速分裂。
Huh?
啊？
Spat, is there
something wrong, pal?
吐口水，有吗
有什么问题吗，朋友？
I would not dare touch such slop
as this, how you say,
我不敢碰这样的泥水
就这样，你怎么说，
Krabby Patty!
蟹蟹帕蒂！
I am designed for the utmost
in culinary cuisine.
我的设计是为了最大限度
在烹饪美食中。
No less!
不少！
But... but I thought
we were friends.
但是……但是我以为
我们是朋友。
Friends with you? Ha!
和你是朋友吗？哈!
We are not even
in the same social class!
我们甚至都不是
在同一个社会阶层！
Have a nice life of mediocrity,
fry cook!
过着平庸的美好生活，
炒菜做饭！
[ wild laughter]
[狂笑]
Le Spatula, wait!
铲子，等等！
I gave up everything for you!
为了你我放弃了一切！
We had something!
我们有东西！
How's thatfor something?
怎么样？
Au revoir, peasant!
再见了，农民！
Have fun ladling
in your greasy spoon!
享受舀勺的乐趣
在你油腻的勺子里！
[ spits loudly]
[大声吐口水]
What happened?!
发生了什么？！
My spatula's gone, Mr. Krabs!
我的铲子不见了，蟹老板！
But how are you
gonna flip Krabby Patties
但你怎么样
会翻转蟹黄馅饼
without a spatu-ler?!
没有铲子？！
I hada spatula once,
我曾经有过一次锅铲，
a realspatula,
一把真正的抹刀，
one that stood by me
through thick and thin,
站在我身边的人
经历了厚重和薄弱，
through grease and gristle,
通过油脂和软骨，
and I betrayed his loyalty...
而我背叛了他的忠诚...
like a fool!
像个傻瓜！
I always did like
your old spatu-ler.
我一直喜欢
你的老铲子。
He got the job done
right every time.
他完成了工作
每次都是对的。
[ gasps]:
You're right, Mr. Krabs.
[喘气]：
你是对的，蟹老板。
The truemeasure of a good
spatula is by his actions,
衡量一个人好坏的真正标准
铲子是通过他的行动，
not by some fancy chrome
and buttons!
不是一些花哨的镀铬物
和按钮！
I've got to find my old spatula!
我得找到我的旧抹刀！
Go to him!
Go now, boy!
去找他吧！
现在就走吧，孩子！
Go before I lose
all me customers!
在我输掉之前走吧
都是我的顾客！
[ sobbing]
[抽泣]
[ beeping]
[嘟嘟声]
[ steady tone]
[稳定的语气]
Spatula?
抹刀？
It can't be true!
这不可能是真的！
[ crying]:
It's too late!
[哭泣]：
太晚了！
SpongeBob, I... I
hate to tell you this.
海绵宝宝，我...我
不想告诉你这个。
I know! He's moved on to that
big kitchen drawer in the sky!
我知道！他已经转向那个了
天空中的大厨房抽屉！
[ sniffles]:
He's... gone!
[抽鼻子]：
他……走了！
Actually,
it's not that.
事实上，
不是那样的。
I didn't get
the acting part.
我没有得到
表演部分。
Oh, I'm so sorry.
哦，我很抱歉。
[ sobbing]Oh, by the way,
[抽泣]哦，顺便说一下，
that's not your spatula.
那不是你的抹刀。
Your buddy's all patched
up in the infirmary.
你的好友已经打好补丁了
在医务室里。
[ gasps]:
Spatula!
[喘气]：
锅铲！
Old buddy!
Oh, I'm so glad you're better!
老伙计！
哦，我很高兴你好多了！
[ squeaks]
[吱吱声]
Spatula, what's wrong?
铲子，怎么了？
[ squeaks]
[吱吱声]
But I didn't mean to betray you.
但我并不是有意背叛你。
Mr. Krabs needed a replacement.
蟹老板需要一个替代者。
Krabby Patties don't flip
themselves, you know.
蟹黄饼不会翻转
他们自己，你知道。
It was a moment
of weakness!
那是一个时刻
弱点！
[ sobbing]:
I'm sorry!
[抽泣]：
对不起！
Oh, what have I done?!
哦，我做了什么？！
What have I done?!
我做了什么？！
[ loud sobbing]
[大声抽泣]
[ loud blubbering]
[大声哭泣]
All that glitters is not gold.
闪光的不一定都是金子。
[ sobbing]
[抽泣]
Good-bye, best friend!
再见，最好的朋友！
[ sobbing]
[抽泣]
[ sobbing, wailing]
[抽泣、哀号]
I'll never find
another spatula like him again.
我永远找不到
又一个像他一样的铲子。
[ sizzling]
[铁板]
Spatula?
抹刀？
You're back!
你回来了！
[ romantic orchestral music
plays]
[ 浪漫管弦乐
播放]
Oh, Spatula,
now that we're together again,
哦，抹刀，
既然我们又在一起了
nothing will ever separate us.
没有什么能将我们分开。
One Monster Krabby Patty.
一只怪物蟹蟹帕蒂。
Okay, buddy, we can do this.
好吧，伙计，我们可以做到。
Ready? One... two...
准备好？一……二……
three!
三！
[ loud snap]
[响亮的响声]
Ooh! [ laughing]
哦！ [笑]
[ SpongeBob laughing]
[海绵宝宝大笑]
Nothing. Ah, well.
没有什么。啊，好吧。
[ clinking]
[叮叮当当]
That sounds like a quarter
crying for help.
听起来像四分之一
哭喊着寻求帮助。
Come to papa!
快来找爸爸吧！
Hold it right there, buddy.
就在那里，伙计。
My son just dropped
that quarter.
我儿子刚摔倒
那个季度。
Yeah? Well, that kid
looks pretty shifty to me.
是的？嗯，那个孩子
对我来说看起来很狡猾。
How do I know
he didn't steal it?
我怎么知道
他没有偷吗？
[ groans]
[呻吟]
Hey!
嘿！
That little brat's throwing
perfectly good money away!
那个小家伙在扔东西
完美的钱走了！
Oh, so if I
can't have it,
哦，所以如果我
不能拥有它，
no one...
没有人...
I hope he throws all your
retirement money down a hole!
我希望他倾尽所有
退休金掉了个洞！
Poor little quarter.
可怜的小季度。
What the...?
什么……？
This well is full of money!
这口井里装满了钱！
Don't worry, little fellas!
别担心，小家伙们！
I'll save you!
我来救你！
[ grunting]
[咕噜声]
Oh, it's no use.
哦，没用的。
Me poop deck's too big.
我的粪便甲板太大了。
Make a wish, dear.
许个愿吧，亲爱的。
All my wishes
have already come true.
我所有的愿望
已经实现了。
Oh, you.
哦，你。
No!
不！
I'll save you, money!
我来救你，钱！
Gotcha!
明白了！
What do you heartless
brutes think you're doing?!
你没心没肺做什么
畜生以为你在做什么？！
Um, using the wishing well.
嗯，使用许愿井。
Well, you toss in a coin
and make a wish.
好吧，你扔一枚硬币
并许愿。
And then what?
然后呢？
And that's it.
就是这样。
Nothing else happens.It's fun!
没有发生任何其他事情，这很有趣！
You mean suckers throw
money down a hole for fun?
你的意思是傻瓜扔
花钱去坑里玩？
That's the greatest scam ever!
这是有史以来最大的骗局！
Can we have our
quarter back now?
我们可以拥有我们的
现在回来了？
SQUIDWARD:
SpongeBob,
章鱼哥：
海绵宝宝，
why aren't those
patties ready?
为什么不是那些
肉饼准备好了吗？
You can't rush
perfection.
你不能着急
完美。
I'm not rushing perfection.
我并不急于追求完美。
I'm rushing you!
我催你了！
[ laughing]
[笑]
Always the kidder,
Squidward.
永远都是个小孩子，
章鱼哥。
[ grumbles]
[抱怨]
Oh, this job stinks!
哦，这个工作太臭了！
But at least I'm not
digging ditches.
但至少我不是
挖沟渠。
KRABS:
Squidward! SpongeBob!
螃蟹：
章鱼哥！海绵宝宝！
I got a new job for you.
我给你找到了一份新工作。
KRABS:
X marks the spot
螃蟹：
X 标记该位置
of the Eugene Krabs memorial
wishing well.
尤金·克拉布斯纪念馆
祝愿。
A wishing well,
here?! Wow!
一口许愿井，
在这里？！哇！
Don't you have to be dead
to have a memorial anything?
你不必死吗
有纪念什么吗？
Oh, Squidward,
don't you believe in magic?
哦，章鱼哥，
你不相信魔法吗？
Yeah, Squidward, don't
you believe in magic?
是啊，章鱼哥，别这样
你相信魔法吗？
No, I don't!
不，我不！
And neither does Mr. Krabs!Well, I do.
蟹老板也没有！嗯，我也有。
This well's gonna make a
lot of dreams come true.
这口井将会产生
很多梦想成真。
What's the first thing
you're gonna wish for?
第一件事是什么
你会想要什么？
To be as far away
from you as possible.
想要尽可能远
尽可能从你那里得到。
Come on, SpongeBob, this hole's
not gonna dig itself.
来吧，海绵宝宝，这个洞
不会自己挖。
And I'm certainly
not gonna do it.
我当然
不会做的。
Squidward, aren't
you excited?
章鱼哥不是吗
你兴奋吗？
This is really
gonna help people.
这真是
会帮助人们。
♪ Take a penny
and some magic ♪
♪ 拿一分钱
还有一些魔法♪
♪ Even though your
life is tragic ♪
Hey!
♪ 即使你的
人生是悲惨的♪
嘿！
♪ You can throw all your dreams
down the well ♪
♪ 你可以抛掉所有的梦想
下井♪
♪ Although every day,
the pain grows ♪
♪ 虽然每天，
痛苦愈演愈烈♪
♪ You'll ride unicorns
on rainbows ♪
♪ 你会骑独角兽
彩虹上♪
♪ If you throw all your dreams
down the well ♪
♪ 如果你抛掉所有的梦想
下井♪
♪ When your life's come apart
at the seams ♪
♪ 当你的生活分崩离析时
在接缝处♪
♪ And you've given up
all your dreams ♪
♪ 而你已经放弃了
你所有的梦想♪
♪ Here is just the means
♪ 这只是手段
♪ To make those dreams
come true ♪
♪ 为了实现这些梦想
成真♪
♪ No more sufferin',
no more sighin' ♪
♪ 不再受苦，
不再叹息♪
Ow!♪ No more pain and
no more cryin' ♪
哎呀！♪ 不再有疼痛，
别再哭了♪
I'm not crying!♪ When you throw all your
dreams down the well ♪
我没有哭！♪ 当你抛下所有的时候
梦见井下♪
Well, Squidward,
what do you think?
嗯，章鱼哥，
你觉得怎么样？
That was the worst song
I ever heard.
那是最糟糕的歌
我曾经听说过。
But at least
this stupid well's finished.
但至少
这口蠢井完蛋了。
It's beautiful!
很美丽！
[ sniffing]
You smell that, boys?
[嗅嗅]
孩子们，你闻到了吗？
That's the
smell of money!
这就是
金钱的味道！
You mean magic,
don't you?
你说的是魔法，
你不是吗？
All I can smell
is that Dumpster.
我能闻到的一切
是那个垃圾箱。
[ flies buzzing]
[苍蝇嗡嗡叫]
All right, Squidward, you
can go back to the register.
好吧，章鱼哥，你
可以回到寄存器。
As long as
there's no singing.
只要
没有歌声。
And I've got a date
with a Krabby Patty.
我有一个约会
和蟹肉饼。
Hold on there,
SpongeBob.
坚持住，
海绵宝宝。
Let me show you
your new station.
让我告诉你
你的新站。
It's kind of
a promotion.
这有点像
促销。
Sort of.
有点像。
A promotion?!
升职？！
Why do I have to go
down in the well?
为什么我必须走
井底下？
To collect the money!
来收钱的！
How long do I
have to stay down here?
我要多久
必须留在这里吗？
See you in eight hours.
八小时后见。
Thanks for the promotion.
感谢您的促销。
It sure is dark
and scary in here.
天肯定黑了
这里很可怕。
[ teeth chattering]
[牙齿打战]
I sure wish I had
a fancy telescope.
我当然希望我有
一个奇特的望远镜
One that works
underwater.
一个有效的
水下。
That'd make me happier
than a june bug
那会让我更快乐
比六月的虫子
at a porch light sale.
在门廊灯销售中。
Our very first wish.
我们的第一个愿望。
I can't wait till
it comes... Oh!
我等不及了
它来了……哦！
I have presented you
with a monetary offering,
我已经向你介绍了
通过货币发行，
as custom dictates.
按照惯例。
My wish, nay, my command,
我的愿望，不，我的命令，
is to be taller.
就是要长高。
Just a little.
只是一点点。
Just big enough
to crush my enemies
够大就好
粉碎我的敌人
like the vermin they are!
他们就像害虫一样！
Gosh... Ow!
天哪...噢！
I wish I had a snazzy new boat.
我希望我有一艘时髦的新船。
I want to be a hotrod mama.
我想成为一名热棒妈妈。
[ gasps]
[喘气]
[ slurping]
[吸吮]
Hey!
嘿！
Oh, my gosh!
Who said that?
哦，天哪！
谁说的？
Patrick...!
帕特里克……！
How do you know my name?
你怎么知道我的名字？
Patrick, this is a wishing well.
帕特里克，这是一个许愿井。
Just throw in a coin
and make a wish.
只需投入一枚硬币
并许愿。
Okay, magical
talking trashcan.
好吧，神奇的
会说话的垃圾桶。
[ coins jingling]
[金币叮当作响]
I wish SpongeBob
were here to see this.
我希望海绵宝宝
我们来这里就是为了看到这个。
Patrick...?!
帕特里克……？！
Hi, SpongeBob.
嗨，海绵宝宝。
I got my wish.
我如愿以偿了。
Patrick, you're
supposed to let go
帕特里克，你是
应该放手
of the coin
when you throw it.
硬币的
当你扔它的时候。
But I got my wish.
但我如愿以偿了。
Well, we got six
and a half hours
嗯，我们有六个
一个半小时
till the end of my shift.
直到我轮班结束。
What do you
want to do now?
你做什么
现在想做什么？
Tag! You're it.
Tag,
you're it.
标签！你就是它。
标签，
你就是它。
Tag! You're it.
标签！你就是它。
Tag,
you're it.
标签！你就是它。
标签，
你就是它。
Tag,
you're it.
Tag! You're it.
标签，
你就是它。
标签！你就是它。
Tag! You're it.
SpongeBob, what kind
of haul did you get?
海绵宝宝，什么类型的
你得到了多少收获？
I did great, Mr. Krabs.
我做得很好，蟹老板。
I got a nickel from Sandy,
two pennies from Mrs. Puff,
我从桑迪那里得到了五分钱
帕夫太太的两便士，
a penny from Plankton, and this
slightly used pair of dentures.
Plankton 的一分钱，还有这个
一副稍微用过的假牙。
And I fell on my head.
我头朝下摔倒了。
Well, I can probably get
a couple of bucks for Patrick.
嗯，我大概可以得到
给帕特里克几块钱。
Nah.
不。
You better just
send up the money.
你最好只是
把钱寄上去。
This wishing well was a
wonderful idea, Mr. Krabs.
这口许愿井是一个
好主意，蟹老板。
Has anyone's wish come true yet?
有人的愿望实现了吗？
Uh... not yet.
呃……还没有。
But I'm sure, if you believe
strong enough,
但我确信，如果你相信
足够强大，
and dug deep enough,
并且挖得足够深，
everyone's wishes
will come true.
大家的愿望
将会实现。
Really?
真的吗？
Yeah, sure, whatever.
是的，当然，无论如何。
Can we come out now?
我们现在可以出来吗？
Goodness, no.
天哪，不。
You gotta stay down there
你必须呆在那里
just in case any late-night
wishers come by.
以防万一深夜
许愿者过来。
I'll be back for you at dawn.
天一亮我就回来接你。
Oh... no one's wishes
are coming true.
唉……没人愿意
即将实现。
What did we do wrong?
我们做错了什么？
I know I believe hard enough.
我知道我足够坚定地相信。
Maybe I just
didn't dig deep enough.
也许我只是
挖得不够深。
What do you say, Patrick?
你说什么，帕特里克？
Are you ready to dig
for some magic?
你准备好挖掘了吗
为了一些魔法？
Yeah!
是的！
♪ Oh, the magic
has gone missin' ♪
♪ 哦，魔法
失踪了♪
♪ And everyone's still wishin'
♪ 每个人都仍然希望
♪ But their dreams have fallen
flat upon the ground ♪
♪ 但他们的梦想已经破灭
平放在地上♪
♪ You'll find magic
under rubble ♪
♪ 你会发现魔法
废墟下♪
♪ So, Patrick, grab a shovel
♪ 所以，帕特里克，拿把铲子
♪ And here is where
the magic can be found ♪
♪ 这就是地方
魔法可以被发现♪
♪ We're at the bottom
of a well ♪
♪ 我们在底部
一口井的♪
♪ But, man, won't it be swell
♪ 但是，伙计，它不会膨胀吗？
♪ When we make everyone's wishes
all come true? ♪
♪ 当我们实现每个人的愿望时
一切都成真了吗？ ♪
Holy mackerel!
圣鲭鱼！
Look, Patrick!
看，帕特里克！
We've struck magic!
我们已经施展魔法了！
Is that good?
这样好吗？
Next to being a fry cook,
除了当一名炒菜厨师，
it's the most important
thing I've ever done.
这是最重要的
我曾经做过的事情。
It's the only thing
I've ever done.
这是唯一的事情
我曾经做过。
SQUIDWARD:
Having fun down there,
SpongeBob?
章鱼哥：
在那里玩得很开心，
海绵宝宝？
[ laughing]
[笑]
Hi, Squidward.Patrick's down there, too?
嗨，章鱼哥。帕特里克也在下面吗？
It just gets
better and better.
它只是得到
越来越好。
Do you want
to make a wish?
你想要吗
许愿吗？
Ha! Ha! I got mywish.
哈!哈!我如愿以偿了。
You two are stuck in a dark hole
and away from me.
你们两个被困在黑洞里
并远离我。
Guess what, Squidward?
你猜怎么着，章鱼哥？
We found the magic.
我们发现了魔法。
[ laughing]
[笑]
There's no magic, SpongeBob.
海绵宝宝，没有魔法。
Wishing wells are just a scam
to fool saps like you.
许愿井只是一个骗局
去愚弄像你这样的傻瓜。
[ laughing]
[笑]
No, it's true.
不，这是真的。
We didfind the magic.
我们确实找到了魔力。
Oh, I wish you
could see it.
哦，我希望你
可以看到它。
Ha, ha, ha... oop!
哈哈哈哈……哎呀！
Squidward, you decided
to join the party.
章鱼哥，你决定了
入党。
Party!
派对！
Let me outta here.
让我离开这里。
We were just gonna
play some party games.
我们只是要
玩一些聚会游戏。
Tag! You're it.Tag! You're it.
标签！就是你了。标记！你就是它。
Tag!
You're it.
I gotta
get outta here.
标签！
你就是它。
我必须
离开这里。
Go, Squidward!
走吧，章鱼哥！
[ screaming, groaning ]
[尖叫、呻吟]
There's no way
to climb outta here.
没有办法
爬出这里。
Maybe if you had more
upper-arm strength.
也许如果你有更多
上臂力量。
Yeah, you should
work out more.
是的，你应该
多锻炼。
Well, why don't I just start
right now?
好吧，我为什么不开始呢
现在？
After all, I got a couple
of dumbbells right here.
毕竟我有一对
哑铃就在这里。
[ laughing]
[笑]
I don't get it.
我不明白。
Would you not
stand so close?
你不会吗
站得这么近？
You're making me
claustrophobic.
你让我
幽闭恐惧症。
What does
claustrophobic mean?
什么是
幽闭恐惧症是什么意思？
It means he's afraid
of Santa Claus.
说明他害怕了
圣诞老人的。
No, it doesn't!
不，没有！
Ho, ho, ho!
嗬，嗬，嗬！
[ giggling]
[咯咯笑]
Stop it, Patrick,
you're scaring him!
别这样，帕特里克，
你吓到他了！
Ho! Ho! Ho!
嗬！嗬！嗬！
It's not working, Patrick.
这不起作用，帕特里克。
Darn.
该死。
Um, Squidward,
嗯，章鱼哥，
You're standing
on my foot.
你站着
在我的脚上。
Oops. Oh, sorry, SpongeBob.
哎呀。哦，对不起，海绵宝宝。
And you got your elbow
in my ribs.
你还得到了你的肘部
在我的肋骨里。
Eww.
呃。
Patrick.
帕特里克.
And stop stepping
in my potato salad.
并且停止脚步
在我的土豆沙拉里。
Hey, hey, hey. Guys!
嘿，嘿，嘿。伙计们！
Stop pushing me, Patrick.
别再逼我了，帕特里克。
You mean like this?
你的意思是这样吗？
No, like this!
不，像这样！
[ slugging]
[重击]
You shouldn't
fight in here.
你不应该
在这里战斗。
This is a magical place.
这是一个神奇的地方。
Patrick,
get off of me!
帕特里克，
放开我！
[ slugging continues]
[继续打斗]
I told you I am claustrophobic.
我告诉过你我有幽闭恐惧症。
Nice try, Squidward,
不错的尝试，章鱼哥，
but there's
no Santa Claus here.
但有
这里没有圣诞老人。
SQUIDWARD:
Patrick!
章鱼哥：
帕特里克！
Good morning, SpongeBob!
早上好，海绵宝宝！
Let's see what you got.
让我们看看你得到了什么。
Boy, it's heavy!
孩子，好重啊！
Must be a lot of money.
一定是很多钱。
Free! I'm free!
自由的！我自由了！
Squidward? What were you
doing down there?
章鱼哥？你是什么
在那儿做什么？
I didn't approve
any overtime.
我没有同意
任何加班。
Or were you sneaking here,
in the dead of night,
或者你偷偷溜到这里，
在夜深人静的时候，
for free wishes?
为了自由的愿望？
The only thing I wish for
is to be far away from here.
我唯一的愿望
就是要离这里很远。
Ow.
噢。
Bye, Squidward.
再见，章鱼哥。
Enjoy your trip.
祝您旅途愉快。
Lucky.
幸运的。
So how much money
did you make last night?
那么多少钱
你昨晚做了吗？
We didn't get any money,
我们没有拿到钱，
but we found
something better.
但我们发现
更好的东西。
We found the magic.
我们发现了魔法。
The what?
什么？
We dug down deeper in the well
and found the magic!
我们把井挖得更深
并发现了魔法！
Now all the wishes
will come true.
现在所有的愿望
将会实现。
Listen closely, SpongeBob.
仔细听，海绵宝宝。
You don't get what you want in
life just by wishing for it.
你没有得到你想要的东西
生活只是因为渴望它。
[ shrieking]
[尖叫]
What in the deep blue is that?
那深蓝色的是什么？
There's a full moon out tonight.
今晚有满月。
Do you like my new
telescope I wished for?
你喜欢我的新作品吗
我想要的望远镜？
That's great, Sandy.
太好了，桑迪。
That wishing well
sure does work.
那口许愿井
当然有效。
Just a coincidence.
只是巧合而已。
What do you think
of my new hotrod?
你觉得怎么样
我的新改装车？
It's beautiful,
Mrs. Puff.
很漂亮，
泡芙女士。
How's about letting me
take it for a spin?
让我怎么样
试一试？
[ both laughing]
[两人都笑了]
No.
不。
See, Mr. Krabs?
She wished for that boat.
看到了吗，蟹老板？
她想要那条船。
You mean she stole
that boat.
你的意思是她偷了
那条船。
Morning, SpongeBob, Krabs.
早上好，海绵宝宝，蟹蟹。
Beautiful day.
美好的一天。
[ crazed laughter]
[疯狂的笑声]
Is that proof enough for you?
这对你来说足够证明了吗？
You'll never get me
to believe in magic. Never!
你永远得不到我
相信魔法。绝不！
Just to prove it to you,
只是为了向你证明，
I'll demonstrate.
我来演示一下。
I wish I was steamed
我希望我被蒸了
and served with a side
of melted butter.
配菜
融化的黄油。
[ laughing]
[笑]
Mr. Krabs! No!
蟹老板！不！
Well, where's your
magic now?
那么，你在哪里
现在魔法吗？
Oh, where am I?
噢，我在哪儿？
What's going on here?
这是怎么回事？
Uh-oh.
呃哦。
I dobelieve in magic.
我确实相信魔法。
I do believe in magic.
Oh, no...!
哦，不……！
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
标题为
WGBH 媒体访问小组
访问.wgbh.org
标题为
WGBH 媒体访问小组
访问.wgbh.org